Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
  - International Investigations
    - India (see also reel 225 for other investigations)
      - Campaign for Indian coffee, Bombay, 1938
    - Kellogg's (Great Britain)
      - London, copy, Rice Krispies--All-Bran corn flakes, undated
      - London--Testing merchandising ideas and methods by means of localised sales, 1937 Sept.
      - Consumer investigation, 1937 Nov.
      - Estimates and schedules, 1938
      - Corn flakes--recommendation price reducing, 1938 Mar.
      - Position analysis, 1938 Aug.
      - Kellogg sales analysis--Jan. to 1938 June, 1938 Sept.
      - Kellogg's position analysis, 1938 July-Sept.
      - Kellogg's position analysis, 1938 Sept.
      - Kellogg's marketing recommendations for 1938, 1938 Oct.
      - Kellogg's position analysis, 1938 Nov.
      - Kellogg's position analysis, 1938 Oct.-Dec.
      - Kellogg's position analysis, 1938 Dec.
      - Kellogg's quarterly analysis of Kellogg's and competitors advertising figures--for fourth quarter of 1938, 1939 Feb.
      - Consumer investigation-1939 Jan., 1939 Feb.
      - Cumulative expenditure for 1938, 1939 Feb.
      - Position analysis, 1939 Jan.
      - Position analysis, 1939 Feb.
      - Position analysis, 1939 Mar.
      - Position analysis, 1939 Jan.-Mar.
      - Position analysis, 1939 Apr.
      - First quarter analysis-1939, 1939 Apr.
      - Check of All-Bran sample in press of hall and cove, 1939 Apr.
      - Check of Krumbles--All-wheat and bran flakes, 1939 Apr.
      - Position analysis, 1939 May
      - Cumulative expenditure Jan.-June, 1939 July
      - Sales analysis Jan.-June, 1939 Aug.
      - Ready prepared cereals--comparison of 1939 investigation with 1937 and 1938, 1939 Aug.
      - Brief survey of marketing and ad policy, 1939 Mar.
      - Summary of cereal investigation 1935-1939 and comparison with investigation 1939, 1939 Mar.
      - Result of cereal investigation 1938-1939, 1939 Mar.
      - Result of cereal investigation 1938-1939 and appendix, 1939 Mar.
    - Australia (See also reels 222, 223)
      - Kellogg's--Hominy meal investigation, 1938 Dec.
    - Canada (See also reels 223, 224)
      - Kellogg's--Consumer survey of ready-to-eat cereals, 1938 Aug.
    - Australia (See also reels 222, 223)
      - Horlick's ad recommendations, press and radio, 1938 Oct. 1-1939 Sept. 30
    - Canada (See also reels 223, 224)
      - Lever Bros. Ltd.--Face washing survey, 1938 Apr.
      - Lever Bros. Ltd.--Face washing survey, 1938 Apr. (Reel 233)
      - Statistical tables, 1938 Apr.
      - Garment tag survey, 1938 Aug.
  - Lever Bros. Co.
    - First Lux investigation in Pittsfield, Fitchburg, Elmira, Kingston, Madison, 1929 Sept.
    - Analysis of 1921-1931 Lux report, 1931 May
    - Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1931 Mar.-May
    - Delineator institute report on Lux tests, 1931 July
    - Consumer investigation of toilet soaps, 1931 July
    - May Stores Co. test chooses Lux, 1932 Apr.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1932 Apr.-Aug.
    - Second Lux test, 1932 Sept.
    - Lux Theatre jury reports on plays (For other jury reports see reels 250--251), 1939 Nov.
  - Pond's Extract Co.
    - Pond's vs. Lady Esther 4 purpose cream #10, 1936 Jan.
    - Cost of one ounce of powders--Pond's, Lady Esther, Woodbury, 1936 Jan.
    - Check on display of Pond's and leading competitive face powders, 1936 Feb.
    - Check on retail outlets on sizes and prices of Pond's and competitors, 1936 Mar.
    - Analysis of sales by products, by sizes, 1936 Mar.
    - Powder investigation in N.Y., 1936 Mar.
    - Test of Pond's new suntan powder, 1936 Apr.
    - Office test on Pond's powder formula MC-4, 1936 Apr.
    - Office test on Pond's powder formula MC-4, revised, 1936 Apr.
    - Face cream consumer survey, April 1936, 1936 May
    - Face cream consumer survey, April 1936, 1936 May
    - Face cream, powder and hand lotion survey among readers of romance, movie and fiction magazines, 1936 May
    - Investigation of distribution and prices of Pond's powder and cream in N.Y. drug stores, 1936 May
    - Pond's cold cream test of formula lE-7-4A, 1936 June
    - Office test on new vitamin creams 143 and 143A, 1936 June
    - Per cent of women with dry, oily or normal skin, 1936 Oct.
    - Report on Pond's Vanishing Cream, 1937 Feb.
    - Pond's tissue investigation on brand and color, 1937 Mar.
    - Dealer survey in Chicago (powder), 1937 May
    - Regular powder vs. Pond's new blend, 1937 June
    - Cold cream test, labeled C-10, 1937 July
    - Check on display of Pond's competitive face powders in 12 N.Y. variety stores, 1937 Sept.
    - Market data, 1937 Sept.
    - Test of new lipstick, 1937 Sept.
    - Photostats of market analysis, 1937 Oct.
    - Face powder test in publications sample, 1937 Nov.
    - Analysis of native white population, 1937 Nov.
    - Analysis of total families by character of population, 1937 Dec.
    - Dealer survey on theatrical cold cream, 1937 Dec.
    - Test of Princess Marguerite face powder, 1938 Jan.
  - Kellogg Co.
    - Kellogg sales analysis, 1938 Aug.
    - Corn flakes trends since radio broadcasts, 1939 Feb.
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Chase & Sanborn coffee (See also reels 49, 56, 57)
      - Radio survey--Flint, Mich., 1936 May
      - Radio survey--San Diego, Calif., 1936 May
      - Copy tests spring 1936, 1936 May
      - Notes on Nielsen coffee meeting at Standard Brands, 1936 May
      - Sales test of red and blue cartons, Dallas and Kansas City divisions, 1936 June
      - Coincidental telephone survey in Grand Rapids, Mich., 1936 June
      - Coffee survey in N.Y. (Coffee making habits), 1936 Oct.
      - Nation-wide mail survey on coffee making habits, 1936 Oct.
      - Fall copy tests, 1936 Nov.
      - Final report on carton tests and sales results after discounting, 1936 Dec.
      - Fall copy tests, 1937 Jan.
      - Test of Chase & Sanborn dated coffee & chicory in New Orleans, fall, 1937 Feb.
      - Test of newspaper ads in Little Rock, Ark., 1937 Feb.
      - Nation-wide consumer survey on coffee making habits, 1937 Feb.
      - Texas blind test, 1937 June
      - Spring copy tests 1937, 1937 June
      - Memo to Mrs. Drenge on coffee at Janssen's Hofbrau, 1937 July
      - Test of 10-day dating plan, 1937 Aug.
      - Crosley survey ratings, 1937 Aug.
      - Nation-wide consumer survey on coffee making habits, 1937 Sept.
      - Information on city market in Buffalo with special reference to food and coffee, Sept., 1937 Oct.
      - Concentration on 94 N.Y. districts of coffee and Tender Leaf Tea, Sept., 1937 Nov.
      - Radio analysis, 1937 Dec.
      - Report by Crosley Inc., Wichita, Kan., 1937 Dec.
      - Test of merchandising in New Brunswick agency, Aug., 1937 Dec.
      - Analysis of Chase & Sanborn sales in Cook County agency, May-Nov. 1937, 1938 Jan.
      - Fall copy tests, 1937, 1938 Jan.
      - Per capita sales of total Seal Brand coffee, by agencies, 1938 Feb.
      - Survey of N.Y. housewives' opinions of Chas. McCarthy spoon as promotion, 1938 Feb.
      - Analysis of possible increase of below average agencies, division per capita,, 1938 Mar.
      - Silver package test, Buffalo division, Oct. 1937-Feb. 1938, 1938 Mar.
      - Analysis cost per request for Chas. McCarthy cutout offer, 1938 Mar.
      - Test of coffees, 26231 and 14263, 1938 Apr.
      - Chase & Sanborn dated coffee and chicory in New Orleans, sales results to Feb. 3, 1938 Apr.
      - Test of coffees, 300471A and 232215B, 1938 Apr.
      - Test of coffees, 25137A and 28475B, 1938 May
      - Test of coffees, 25129A and 23647B, 1938 May
      - Nation-wide consumer survey on coffee making habits, 1938 May
      - Test of coffees, 22181A and 26769B, 1938 June
      - Test of coffees, 16457A and 14269B, 1938 June
      - Test of coffees, 22180A and 25125B, 1938 June
      - Test of coffees, 21261A and 30150B, 1938 June
      - Analysis of cost per request for Chas. McCarthy spoon offer, 1938 Sept.
      - Chase & Sanborn dated coffee and chicory in New Orleans, sampling, 1938 Aug.
      - Use of painted bulletins in Cleveland, Detroit and Houston, 1938 Oct.
      - Crosley Inc. telephone survey in Wilkes-Barre during Chase & Sanborn radio program, 1938 Oct.
      - Estimated consumption and U.S. per capita consumption of coffee and tea in W.Va., 1938 Nov.
      - Chart showing ads and sales, 1938 Nov.
      - Consumer investigation in New Orleans on Chase & Sanborn dated coffee and chicory, 1938 Dec.
      - Analysis of Chas. McCarthy game request and summary of offer, 1939 Jan.
    - Fleischmann's Yeast
      - Survey on vitamins among JWT office members, 1937 Nov.
      - Summary of A, B, and C metropolitan districts, 1937 Nov.
      - Life Begins at Forty, letter study, 1937 Nov.
      - Advertising recommendations 1938 and plan for test campaigns 1938, 1937 Dec.
      - Breakdown of 1937 Fleischmann budget by divisions, 1937 Dec.
      - Yeast for Baking, advertising recommendations 1938, 1937 Dec.
      - Analysis of sales and advertising coverage in New England, New York, Philadelphia and Buffalo divisions, 1938 Jan.
      - Investigation among adolescents who sent for Arthur Murray dance book, 1938 Jan.
      - Yeast for Health, percent change 1936 vs. 1937, 1938 Feb.
      - Estimate of influence of radio on N.E. sales, Oct.-Dec. 1937, 1938 Feb.
      - Yeast for Dogs, survey among owners, etc. of dogs, 1938 Feb.
      - Net income of Standard Brands and Fleischmann's yeast, 1938 Apr.
      - Analysis of pound yeast customers, Jan. 1937, first trial, 1938 Jan.
      - Analysis of pound yeast customers, July 1937, second trial, 1938 Jan.
      - Analysis of pound yeast customers, Jan. 1938, third trial, 1938 Jan.
      - Pound yeast sales trends, 1938 Jan.
      - Sales by volume groups based on Fleischmann deliveries on Arizona, Albuquerque, Southern and Texas scale, 1938 Jan.
      - Advertising expenditures, 1938 Dec.
      - Analysis of sales and advertising coverage in New England vs. U.S., 1938 vs. 1937, 1938 Apr.
      - Vitamin copy tests, fall 1937, 1938 May
      - Trend of sales by drug chain of vitamin concentrate, 1937, 1938 May
      - Sales of health drinks in drug chains in eastern part of U.S., 1938 May
      - Fleischmann foil yeast, charts on sales in N.E. division, 1938 May
      - Memo on vitamin sales figures (Vi-Syneral), 1938 May
      - Test of new Forvitan (Yeast) formula, 1938 May
      - Copy tests, spring 1938, also comparison Mar.-Apr. 1938 vs. Mar.-Apr. 1937, 1938 May
      - Division of foil sales between health, baking and other purposes, 1938 June
      - Foil sales in agencies with household yeast and sales in divisions, 1938 June
      - Preliminary study of possibilities for marketing toasted yeast flakes, 1938 June
      - Comments on proposed survey on foil yeast for baking, 1938 June
      - Memo on trend of dry yeast sales in Canada, 1938 July
      - Yeast for Health advertising recommendations, fall 1938, 1938 July
      - Recommendation on increasing size and price of foil yeast, 1938 Aug.
    - Tender Leaf Tea
      - Consumer test of 4 teas, 1934 Nov.
      - Tea strainer investigation in New Rochelle, N.Y., 1934 Dec.
      - Copy tests, first quarter 1935, 1935 May
      - Consumer and dealer survey on market for tea, 1935 June
      - Plan for investigation of market for tea, 1935 Apr.
      - Tea display test in new jersey, 1936 Mar.
      - Test in Family Circle, Nov.-Dec. 1935, 1936 Mar.
      - Results of coincidental phone survey, Cincinnati, 1936 Apr.
      - Good Housekeeping seal on display, tested in N.J., 1936 Apr.
      - Consumer survey in 6 southern cities, 1936 Apr.
      - Test in Family Circle, Mar.-May 1936, 1936 June
      - Copy tests, Mar.-May 1936, 1936 July
      - Test of radio in Cincinnati, 1936 July
      - Copy tests, spring 1936, supplementary report, 1936 July
      - Paper tea balls test, 1937 Apr.
      - Consumer and dealer tea survey, 1929-1937, 1937 May
      - Copy tests, preliminary report, Mar.-May 1938, 1937 June
      - Trend of sales, Philadelphia division, 1937 July
      - Letter to Mr. Stetler and requests received for Teddy's Diary, 1937 July
      - Copy tests, final report, Mar.-June 1937, 1937 Sept.
      - Radio analysis, 1937 Dec.
      - Crosley survey on radio programs, Wichita, Kan., 1937 Dec.
      - Lipton's tea, national advertising expenditures by major media, first 9 months, 1938 Feb.
      - Sampling campaign in Gillespie, Ill., also revision, 1938 Feb.
      - Per capita sales, by agencies, 1937, 1938 Feb.
      - Analysis of possible increase if below average agencies were brought up to division capital, 1938 Mar.
      - Spring copy tests 1938, 1938 Aug.
      - Cities cancelled for 1938 and sales for first 6 months, 1938 Aug.
      - Consumer test of 2 tea bags, X and Y, 1938 Sept.-Oct.
      - Analysis of sales in cities where radio was cancelled, 1938 Oct.
      - Advertising expenditures, 1938 Dec.
      - Tea balls, sampling campaign in Wilmington, 1938 Dec.
      - Analysis of sales in cities where radio was cancelled, 1939 Feb.
      - Spring copy test, 1939, 1939 Sept.
      - Estimated advertising for 1940, 1940 Jan.
      - Dealer and consumer survey in Buffalo, N.Y., 1940 Mar.
      - Double Your Money Back test, 1940 Apr.-May
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Apr. 1940, 1940 May
  - Skol Co., Inc.
    - Consumer investigation on sunburn preparations, 1937 Sept.
    - Second consumer investigation on sunburn preparations, 1937 Oct.
    - Survey on market for sunglasses in 4 cities, 1937 Oct.
    - Odor and color test of Skol, 1938 Jan.
    - Ointment and sunburn remedy sales, chain stores in eastern U.S., 1938 Jan.
    - Dealer investigation in Florida, 1938 Apr.
    - Trend in sales of suntan lotions, creams and pads in drug, department and variety stores, 1938 Aug.
    - Memo to Mr. Resor on insect repellents, 1940 July
    - Office test on 2 samples of insect repellents, A and B, 1940 Sept.
  - Lux Group (Mr. Hinks: for approvals and releases see reel 249)
    - Gallup reports (In chronological order; many dates missing; see reel 251 for more 1933 reports), 1933-1939 (Reel 250)
    - Lux Radio Theatre of the Air (Many dates missing), 1935-1940
    - Lux Radio Theatre of the Air (Many dates missing), 1937-1940
  - Lever Brothers (see reel 46, 47, 199 for other investigations)
    - Lux toilet soap, office investigation on odor preference, 1930 Aug. (Reel 251)
    - Lux Flakes, add a handful ads, 1932 Sept.
    - Lux Flakes, bath test, 1937 Sept.
    - Lux Group--Gallup reports (continued from reel 250), 1933 Jan.-June
    - Analysis of advantages and disadvantages of large size unscented cake of soap
    - Lux for dishwashing, mail, 1925 Feb.
    - Hard water investigation, Butterick Publishing, 1925
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1929
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1930 June
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1931 May
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1931 July
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1931 Oct.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1931 Sept.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1931 Dec.
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 Jan.-Feb.
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 Mar.
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 June
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 Aug.
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 June-July
    - Lux Flakes, Lux toilet soap test campaign, 1932 Sept.
    - Lever Brothers products, Los Angeles times survey, 1932 Apr.
    - Lux toilet soap, presentation copy, 1933 Jan.
    - Lux Flakes, dealer attitude, 1933 Feb.
    - Lever Brothers investigation on washing men's socks and underwear, 1933 July
    - Summary of objections to various brands of toilet soaps, 1933 Aug.
    - Consumer investigation on care of men's socks, 1933 Sept.
    - Lux Flakes third test campaign, 1932 Nov.
    - Lux toilet soap test, 1932 Nov.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, 1932 Dec.
    - Lux toilet soap test campaign, tests 2, 3, 4, 5, 1933 Mar.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, test 5x, 1933 Apr.
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, test 3x and 4x, 1933 June
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, test 6x, 1933 July
    - Lux Flakes test campaign, test 7x, 1933 Sept.
    - Mr. Gilman's comments on 1934 ads, 1933 Oct.
    - Lux toilet soap, presentation copy, 1934
    - Lux toilet soap, national soap survey, 1934 Apr.
    - Lux toilet soap contest, 1935 Feb.
    - General soap survey, 1935 Nov.
  - Hartford, Conn.
    - Survey of public attitudes toward national defense and toward newspapers, 1941 Aug. (Reel 256)
  - Lever Brothers (see reel 46, 47, 199 for other investigations)
    - Sample copy, Lux 1936 campaign, 1936
    - Lux toilet soap, presentation copy, 1936
    - Survey in N.Y. City of washing dresses, 1936 Aug.
    - Women's World Subscriber questionnaire on soap, 1934 Feb.
  - Pond's Extract Co. (Lamont-Corliss, distributor)
    - Magazines, as compared with urban and rural markets of U.S., 1937 Oct.
  - Block Drug Co.
    - Memo to Mr. Richardson re: plan for Gold Medal Haarlem Oil survey, 1942 June
    - Survey in Daw's drug stores on Haarlem Oil, Rochester N.Y., 1942 July
    - Dr. Killian's taste test, Gold Medal Haarlem Oil capsules, 1942 Aug.
    - Gold medal substitution survey, N.Y. City, 1942 Aug.
    - Mail survey among persons responding to the Dentu-Grip free offer over WIW Cincinnati (May 1942) plan, 1942 Sept.
    - Dentu-Grip distribution check, 1943 Jan.
    - Nation wide consumer survey in Dentu-Grip, 1943 Feb.
    - Plan for Gold Medal Haarlem Oil re: continuing survey of users, 1943 Mar.
    - Analysis of U.S. negro market (table), 1943 Apr.
    - Gold medal Haarlem Oil consumer survey in Binghamton, N.Y., 1943 Mar.
    - Gold medal Haarlem Oil capsules distribution in Detroit Polish section--Memo to Mr. Relsey Denton, 1943 Sept.
    - Memo to Mr. Relsey Denton re: Gold Medal distribution in N.Y. City (lower East Side) Jewish section, 1943 Nov.
    - Survey by inserts in packages, 1943 Nov.
    - Survey by inserts in packages--Gold medal Haarlem Oil Corp., 1943 Nov.
    - Gold medal Haarlem Oil Corp.--Survey by inserts in packages, 1944 May
  - P. Lorillard Co.--Old Gold cigarettes
    - Work sheets on Old Gold national survey, 1940 Dec.
    - Survey of opinion of cigarette smokers, 1940 Dec.
    - Columbus, Ohio--Cigarette survey, 1940 Dec.
    - Old Gold sales in selected cities, 1940 Dec.
    - Results of cigarette test--Old Gold vs. regular brand, 1940 Dec.
    - Summary of information on 70 smoking cigarette, 1941 Jan.
    - Memo on Old Gold copy test, 1941 Jan.
    - Investigators impressions--Old Gold survey, 1941 Jan.
    - Extent of knowledge of change in Old Gold blend, 1941 Jan.
    - Charts on cigarette market, 1941 Jan.
    - Map--State breakdown of 1941 Old Gold budget vs. sales and population, 1941 Feb.
    - Men and women interviewed at random--N.Y., 1941 Mar.
    - Old Gold and competitive cigarette advertising expenditures, 1941 Apr. and May
    - Dealer merchandising survey, 1941 May
    - Cigarette advertising recall (Questionnaire), 1941 Apr.
    - Parkchester apartments--Readership investigation, 1941 Nov.
  - Pond's Extract Co. (See also reels--#52, #53, # 221, # 233) Pond's cream lotion
    - Lotion test at McCall's, 1936 Feb.
    - Hand lotion test--#165 and #10, 1936 Feb.
    - Hand lotion test, 1936 Aug.
    - Test of dispenser top and hand lotion, 1936 Oct.
    - Test of Pond's Danya (#194-S/L-#5), 1936 Feb.
    - Test of dispenser top on 55 cents size bottle of Danya lotion, 1937 June
    - Danya dispenser top, 1938 Mar.
    - Test of dispenser top, 1938 jun.
    - Office investigation on hand lotion, 1938 Dec.
    - Preliminary Danya mail and telephone survey, 1939 May
    - Danya mail survey, 1939 May
    - Review of Danya odor tests made from 1936 through May 1939, 1939 jun.
    - Odor test of Danya hand lotion (A and B), 1939 jun.
    - N.Y and Chicago Office questionnaires on hand lotion, 1940 Mar.
    - Danya mail survey, 1940 Apr.
    - Danya hand lotion test, 1940 Aug.
    - Office survey on hand lotion, 1941 Feb.
    - Danya survey (Pink vs. white), 1941 Apr.
    - Wide variations in returns from Women's Day control advertising--Danya, 1941 May
    - Lotion test (K vs. L), 1941 May
  - J.B. Williams Co. (See also reels-#61 and #221)
    - Aqua Velva sampling survey, 1936 Sept.
    - Glider test in 4 cities, 1936 Nov.
    - Magazine preferences of Shave-a-Day men, 1936 Nov.
    - Analysis of total drug store business in U.S., 1936 Nov.
    - Soap odor test--Colgate vs. Williams, 1936 Dec.
    - Analysis of sales of Williams gift sets in downtown Chicago drug stores during Christmas season, 1937 Jan.
    - Suggested Williams sales territories, 1937 Mar.
    - Jobber and dealer stock check in 6 cities on holiday sets, 1937 Mar.
    - Estimated dollar sales, 1936, 1937 Mar.
    - Williams Glider length of use test, 1937 Apr.
    - Success of revolving stands in drug stores, 1937 May
    - Agua Velva carton mail investigation, 1937 jun.
    - Memo to Mr. Meek on consumer--Investigation, 1937 Jul.
    - Analysis of Williams' domestic business, 1937 Jul.
    - Analysis of Williams' sales, 1937 Jul.
    - Magazine preference of Williams dealers (Memo), 1937 Jul.
    - Shaving soap survey in 4 large metropolitan centers, 1937 Jul.
    - Supplementary report on 200 consumer interviews in Houston and Dallas--Texas, 1937 Aug.
    - High-Priced toilet soaps and inexpensive toilet kits for men, 1937 Aug.
    - Memo on Chicago mail investigation, 1937 Sept.
    - Shaving stick test, 1937 Oct.
  - Branch Office Reports (See reel #49 also)
    - Survey among meat packers on institutionalizing meat promotion (Chicago), 1937 Mar.
    - Report on market possibilities for Hall's Wines Tonic in the U.S. (London Office), 1938 Jan.
    - Interviews with buyers on National Sewing Machine new lightweight portable (Chicago Office), 1938 Jan.
    - Plan for survey of American opinion relative to World's Fair exhibits of foreign nations (London Office), 1938 Feb.
    - Retail interviews in regard to the giant panda. (Chicago), 1938 Feb.
    - Report on U.S. market for Syminton's Granulated Gravy, 1938 Mar.
    - Quaker Oats grocery store display (London Office information), 1938 Mar.
    - National Breweries Ltd. sales and advertising costs (Montreal Office), 1938 Mar.
    - Consumer and dealer survey on olives (San Francisco Office), 1938 Mar.
    - Hershey chocolate (Montreal Office), 1938 Mar.
    - Miscellaneous information on Summit N.J. (Union Center) (Wall St. Office), 1938 Mar.
    - National Breweries, Ltd--Beer survey in Montreal (Montreal), 1938 Apr.
  - Branch Office Reports Bk. 3
    - Tea Garden preserves--Kitchen test (Chicago Office), 1936 Feb.
    - Report on interviews with reception desk clerks--United, American and T.W.A. airlines (Chicago), 1937 Aug.
    - George Washington coffee in tubes (London Office), 1938 May
    - General Shoe Corp.--Men's Apparel Qualities Guild re: World's Fair exhibit (Chicago), 1938 May
    - Food and beverage market (Especially liquid chocolate) (London), 1938 Aug.
    - Test in 4 publication surveys on window cleaners (London Office), 1938 Aug.
    - Memo on information about Fifty-Fifty--a drink no longer available (London Office), 1938 Sept.
    - Food Advertisers Service (Chicago Office), 1938 Oct.
    - Dr. Jackson's Meal (Canadian Office), 1938 Nov.
    - Consumption of fluid milk--in Boston, Philadelphia and New York (Seattle Office), 1939 Mar.